driversdownloader.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Company

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register and become a DriversDownloader member in order to participate on the forums, enter into a contest, or opt-in our email newsletters. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.

To help you quickly find services or information on DriversDownloader.

To help us create content most relevant to you.

To alert you about updated information and other new services on DriversDownloader.

Collection of data

Registration for an account on this site requires only a valid e-mail address and a user name that has not been chosen already. You are not required to provide any other information if you do not want to. Please be aware that the user name you choose, the e-mail address you provide and any other information you enter may render you personally identifiable, and may possibly be displayed on this web site intentionally (depending on choices you make during the registration process, or depending on the way in which the site is configured) or unintentionally (subsequent to a successful act of intrusion by a third party). As on many web sites, the site editor may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if it is indeed the site editor's policy to display advertising) is set forth below.

Security

DriversDownloader strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction

Distribution of personal information

DriversDownloader does not distribute personal information to any third parties. Should this change, DriversDownloader will not distribute any information without your prior express consent. Please be aware that it may be possible, depending on your use of various features on DriversDownloader, that some of your personal information is available on publicly accessible web pages. One example would be using the DriversDownloader Forums. Consent to expose some of your personal information in these cases is implied by the use of these features.

Use of data

Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site editor's policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor's legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this web site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites.

Cookies

Like many web sites, this web site sets and uses cookies to enhance your user experience Ñ to remember your personal settings, for instance. Advertisements may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site.You can visit the Network Advertising Initiative if you want to find out more information about this practice, and to learn about your options, including your options with regard to the following companies that may serve advertising on this site:

Enforcement

If for some reason you believe DriversDownloader has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at [Support@DriversDownloader.com](mailto:Support@DriversDownloader.com), and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line

Editing or deleting your account information

You are provided with the ability to edit the information stored for your user account information during registration, by visiting your user account control panel. You can request that your user account be deleted; to do so, please contact the site administrator. Content or other data that you may have provided, and that is not stored within your user account, such as articles published, may continue to remain on the site at the site editor's discretion, even after your user account is deleted. Please see the site's Terms of use for more information.

Changes to this document

Changes to this document may be made any time without warning. DriversDownloader.com may or may not notify you of changes in this policy, however, we will make an effort to notify you if there are any major changes to this policy. You will not be notified about changes related to clarification and/or elaboration of parts of this policy

Contact information

If you have any questions about this policy or about DrviersDownloader.com, please feel free to contact us.

Our email are support#driversdownloader.com (Please replace # into @)
